netmedicos.com 2005-03-05

# NETMEDICOS.COM | Privacy Policy PLAB, IELTS, USMLE, GRE, AIPGMEE, AIIMS, AFMC, BHU, CMC, JIPMER, PGI, SGPGI, ...

| 

_**Privacy Policy:**_  
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.   
The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our site.

  * The registration form on our website, requires users to give us contact information (such as their name, date of birth, email, etc). This information is used to get in touch with them when necessary. We don't share your email and personal information with any one.  
 
  * Our site uses cookies. This is to remember your login name and pass it between forms. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information to improve our services and for site management purposes.  
 
  * Our site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party websites.  
 
  * Any information that is disclosed in our forums, message boards or shout box becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  
 
  * We allow the users email submission for changing and modifying information previously provided.  
 
  * If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with us, you can use the feedback / contact us form.

|    

|  FEEDBACK  
---  
  
Enter your name, email id, & comments / queries and click submit
